# Joseph Toledo

(289) 600-7173

josephnicotoledo@gmail.com

Dear Sir/ Madame,

I am writing in the hopes that my qualifications can accommodate any open positions there may be within your establishment.

When provided with a task, I dedicate myself in completing it to the best of my abilities while always providing the highest quality of service. I will ensure that my contributions towards the company will help to achieve any goals it may have. With the experiences I have gained through working in retail, I've been trained to worked efficiently and can communicate clearly with customers so that they are satisfied with their experience.

Enclosed is my resume. I look forward to hearing from you and potentially being able to contribute to your company in the future.

Sincerely,

Joseph Toledo

# **Joseph Toledo**

(289) 600-7173

josephnicotoledo@gmail.com

**Profile:** I am a versatile, hardworking, and cooperative individual who is capable of quickly adapting to new workplaces. When interacting with others, I can communicate confidently in a well-ordered manner.

### **Work Experience:**

# Whitby Urgent Care Walk-In Clinic (Whitby, ON)

Senior Medical Receptionist 03/2018 - 12/2021

- Registered patients into the EMR computer software and created their files to manage their health concerns and follow-up visits
- Ensured that patients were comfortable in the waiting room and escalated issues to the physicians when situations became severe
- Took patient's basic vitals (i.e. Blood pressure, oxygen saturation, temperature etc.)
- Responsible for cleaning the clinic during open hours and once closed
- Would receive and maintain the inventory of our vaccines and equipment

# F.G Bradley's (Oshawa, ON)

Sales Associate 04/2017 - 01/2018

- Spoke with customers and offered information regarding our products
- Maintained organized, presentable merchandise to drive continuous sales
- Trained and developed new sales associates in products, store maintenance and procedures

#### Bulk Barn (Oshawa, ON)

Sales Associate 05/2013 – 08/2016

- Responsibilities included roles such as cashier and stock person
- Responded to customer's questions about our products
- Organized and restocked the shelves/bins to maintain store visual appeal and cleanliness

## **Relevant Skills:**

- Communication Skills: can speak effectively/ listen attentively and write at an advanced level
- Management Skills: can express opinions and problem solves well
- <u>Computer Skills</u>: can operate hardware (such as computers or other machinery) and software (such as Microsoft Office, beginner level coding proficiency in Python, HTML, CSS, and JavaScript)

#### **Education:**

Graduated from Monsignor Paul Dwyer CHS (2012 - 2016) as an Ontario Scholar with completion in the French Delf Exam A2 Level

Graduated from Ontario Tech University with a Bachelor's Degree in Biological Sciences - Life Sciences with a minor in Chemistry

References available upon request